cw.com.hk 2003-04-17

# IDG Communications - Hong Kong : Privacy

## IDG Hong Kong Online Privacy Statement

[](https://www.truste.org/validate/7693)IDG Communications (HK) Ltd is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for idg.com.hk, cw.com.hk and pcworld.com.hk. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the Webmaster by e-mail at [webmasterhk@idg.com.hk](mailto:webmasterhk@idg.com.hk). 

If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the "[TRUSTe WatchDog Dispute Resolution Process](http://www.truste.org/watchdog.html)" TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

This statement explains the Internet privacy practices of IDG Communications (HK) Ltd., including the IDG.com.hk, Computerworld Hong Kong Online and PCWorld Hong Kong Online Web sites.

Our goal is to gain our readers' trust and confidence by promoting the use of fair information practices. To better explain our commitment to protecting your privacy, we have provided detailed information concerning our privacy policy for your reference:

  1. What personally identifiable information this web site collects from you and how the information is used.
  2. With whom this site shares the information it collects.
  3. How you can correct or make changes to this information.
  4. What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use, and distribution of information.
  5. What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under IDG Hong Kong's control. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at: 

Customer Service - Online Privacy  
IDG Communications (HK) Ltd  
Suite 601, K. Wah Centre  
191 Java Road, North Point  
Hong Kong  
Tel: +(852) 2861-3238  
Fax: +(852) 2861-0953  
E-mail: [webmasterhk@idg.com.hk](mailto:webmasterhk@idg.com.hk)

### What information does IDG Hong Kong's Web sites collect and how is it used?

IDG Hong Kong's Web sites collects optional data supplied by visitors to our web site through registration, surveys, sweepstakes or contests, as well as information that we gather from visitors via our server log, such as. IP addresses, access date and time, browser type and version, referrer URLs of all visitors. This data is used solely for the purpose of analyzing traffic on IDG Hong Kong's Web sites. This information enables us to better tailor our content to your interests, and to help our advertisers better understand the audience they are reaching. Our site is completely free, and is supported by paid advertisements and it is therefore critically important for us to be able to identify our audience. Information is only shared with advertisers or any other third parties in aggregate form. We are also firmly committed to identifying whether information presented on our sites is written by our editorial staff or is contributed by a user or vendor.

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**Ad Serving Technology**

IDG.com has contracted with DoubleClick to serve all advertising on http://www.idg.com, both on the Web site and through our email newsletters. When DoubleClick serves ads to the user, it uses cookies to track certain types of non-personally identifiable information: for example, a user's IP address, browser version or type, operating system, service provider, and local time. In addition, IDG.com uses clear GIFs, or pixel tags, provided by DoubleClick to allow the browser's cookie to be recognized when the browser visits IDG.com. Information collected and shared through this technology is not personally identifiable (i.e., it does not include your name, address, telephone number, or email address). DoubleClick does share non-personally identifiable information, such as user profiles based on clickstream profile data, with IDG.com, but strictly in aggregate form. For more details about the information DoubleClick collects and the opportunity to opt out of such data collection, please visit: <http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/>. 

**IP Addresses**

For each visitor to our site, our web server automatically records the visitor's domain and IP address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. IDG Hong Kong makes no attempt to link these IP addresses with personal information, such as names or e-mail addresses, under any circumstance.

**Newsletter**

In order to subscribe to our various newsletters <http://www.idg.com.hk/subscription/> we do require the following information to be provided to us such as, your name, title, address, phone number, fax number and or email address. The fields are clearly marked within each field for proper identification.You can also unsubscribe your newsletter, you will receive an e-mail confirming your information has been deleted from our database. No more personal data will be keep for future use.

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our subscription form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who subscribe to our services, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instruction in the e-mail, e-mail us at [circ_hk@idg.com.hk](mailto:circ_hk@idg.com.hk) or write request to our Circulation Department.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**E-mail-To-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's and their name and email address. IDG Hong Kong will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. IDG Hong Kong stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

**E-mail Links**

We use e-mail links located on the "contact us" page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have.We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments to improve the site and program, or review and discard the information. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission.

### How is our registration data used? 

Some optional services that IDG Hong Kong offers require registration. Our site's registration process requests that users give us contact information (like their name and email address), unique identifiers for authentication, and demographic information that pertains to their profession such as business industry and job function. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user relevant information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners, but only to those who opt to receive it. We deliver these messages, and we never allow email addresses or other contact information out of our control. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary, for the administration of prizes, rewards, or to respond to customer service requests. We also use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is only shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Unique identifiers such as passwords, are collected to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our database. 

### What does IDG Hong Kong's relationship with third party Web sites?

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we IDG Hong Kong are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### What are cookies and how does IDG Hong Kong's Web sites use them?

Cookies are small files that contain information a web site uses for tracking a visit. Our site uses cookies to authenticate who you are and what information you have registered for access to. We also use this to keep track of your service selections and to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. You password is encrypted within the cookie, so this cannot be accessed by any outside parties. As an option, a visitor may choose to reject a cookie and instead use their personal identifier each time they visit and select services that require authentication. Not all areas of our sites require authentication.

We use an outside serving company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

### With whom this site shares the information it collects?

As a general rule, IDG Hong Kong does not share your personal information with third parties. IDG Hong Kong may use personal information in the aggregate for marketing and promotional purposes. In addition, IDG Hong Kong may share personal information collected in connection with a sweepstakes or contest with a third-party sponsor of that contest or sweepstakes, if applicable. However, personal information may be shared with the individual sponsor of a contest, promotion, or sweepstake, and only if the participant specifically asks to receive additional information from a specific sponsor and for the purposes of administering the contest and notifying the winners. 

However, IDG Hong Kong occasionally informs registered users and mail-list subscribers of special deals, new products, and other third-party product and service offers that it believes they will find interesting. IDG Hong Kong mail-list subscribers are given the option to opt out of receiving such mailings during the registration process.

You may request that your information not be used for such purposes by sending an e-mail request to IDG Hong Kong's Webmaster at [webmasterhk@idg.com.hk](mailto:webmasterhk@idg.com.hk). Under no circumstances are e-mail lists made available to known spammers, get-rich-quick sites, or pornographic sites.

### What is IDG Hong Kong's relationship with the DoubleClick advertising network?

IDG Hong Kong has contracted with DoubleClick to serve all advertising on IDG Hong Kong's family of Web sites, both on the Web site itself and through its e-mail newsletters. When DoubleClick is serving ads to the user, it is also using cookies to track certain types of non-personally identifiable information, such as a user's IP address, browser version or type, operating system, service provider, and time zone. For more details about the non-personally identifiable information DoubleClick collects and the opportunity to opt out of such data collection, please visit [www.doubleclick.net:8080/privacy_policy/](http://www.doubleclick.net:8080/privacy_policy/).

Although DoubleClick does share with IDG Hong Kong non-personally identifiable information such as user profiles based on clickstream profile data, such information is strictly in the aggregate. Any pages a user calls up on IDG Hong Kong's family of Web sites are not connected with personally identifiable information collected either at IDG Hong Kong's family of Web sites or elsewhere. 

### Partner / co-branded sites

IDG Hong Kong has several partners that produce IDG Hong Kong branded services. Information that is shared with or collected at partner sites is used to provide the services that the user selects at that site. Communication by our partners with IDG Hong Kong customers is limited to the services that our customers select. For example, if a customer requests to be notified when information on a selected topic becomes available, the partner site may contact our customers. Customers are given the option to discontinue services at any time. Additionally a user name and password may be shared with partner sites for the purpose of logging a customer in to an IDG Hong Kong's service hosted in another domain. If desired, customers may choose to exclude the sharing of this information during the registration process, or by modifying their profile and service selections. Our partner sites currently include: 

**Co-branded service**

@myMail.IDG.com.hk

IT KnowledgeBank

### How can I correct or make changes to my personal information?

Subscribers to mail-list services can change or delete their personal identifying information by visiting the sites and clicking on the appropriate Unsubscribe or Change Subscription buttons. For all other changes, please contact IDG Hong Kong's Webmaster at [webmasterhk@idg.com.hk](mailto:webmasterhk@idg.com.hk).

What choices and rights are available to me regarding the collection, use, and distribution of my personal information?   
The decision to share your personal information is taken very seriously by our team. Should you have any questions about the collection, use, or distribution of your personal information, please contact us directly at: 

Customer Service - Online Privacy  
IDG Communications (HK) Ltd  
Suite 601, K. Wah Centre  
191 Java Road, North Point  
Hong Kong  
Tel: +(852) 2861-3238  
Fax: +(852) 2861-0953  
E-mail: [webmasterhk@idg.com.hk](mailto:webmasterhk@idg.com.hk)

### What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under IDG Hong Kong's control?

IDG Hong Kong Web sites have security measures in place to protect the loss,misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Internally, IDG Hong Kong restricts access to personally identifiable information. These hardened security systems include firewalls, authenticated access to internal databases, and audit of regular procedures. Only employees who need access to the information in order to do their jobs have access. These employees are limited in number, and are committed to our privacy and security policies. In order to try to minimize this risk, we encrypt all information that you submit in ordering one of our products or services using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web sites.
